I challenged the biggest creators
on YouTube
to try to beat this game
for $250,000.
[cheering]
Let's go!
Run, run, run!
I separated these 8 teams
into their own lobbies,
and the first 4 teams to make it
to the end together will move on.
Just lock in. Lock in.
We got this.
Make sure you're sprinting.
Alright. Trampoline. Jump!
Good. Alright, here we gotta break it.
We gotta break this wall
to open it.
Yup, yup. Nice, nice.
Keep going.
You need everyone on the platform!
Stop, stop, stop.
Keep going.
Let’s go, let’s go.
Alright, there we go.
Now you can move on.
- Karl, come on!
- Karl, we're on the platform!
So far, no teams have finished.
I really hope you guys
enjoy this video.
This is a phenomenal set,
and we literally have 32 creators here.
There’s fire.
Just go around.
Oh my God,
that was clutch.
Oh I'm so sorry guys,
I fell in the lava.
Keep going.
Oh, there’s lasers!
Just don’t stop.
Just keep on going.
Don’t get knocked off.
Switch, switch, switch.
It's off.
Yeah, I'm-- I’m towards the end.
We're here, we're here.
I'm coming.
Take your time on the hammers.
[screams] Guys!
- Come on, come on!
- Go, go, go! [screams]
Oh, we got our first finish!
[cheering]
Let's go team!
We gotta be the winners.
Come on.
I'm at the end.
You’re so close.
One more, one more.
Get on the button!
[cheering]
We got our second finish.
Only two teams remain!
We can't get eliminated.
Come on.
We made it, I made it.
Get over here.
No!
The Mr Beast team's about to lose.
Guys, it's our channel!
We're waiting on Karl and Tareq!
[screams]
I’m almost there.
Jump and you got it!
Let's go!
[cheering]
One spot remains!
Who are we waiting on?
You’re right there, Jeza.
Ok, ok.
Only one spot. One spot!
No!
Gotta go over, dash over.
Come on.
Yes!
[cheering]
And we have our final spot!
No!
That was so close.
Unfortunately,
if you're standing in front of an X,
you have been eliminated.
I need you to exit the set.
And to those of you that are still here,
you're one step closer
to winning your fans $250,000.
Everyone head up
to the 2nd layer.
- How we feeling grey team?
- Confident.
Yellow team, only one team's
getting eliminated this round.
Is it gonna be you guys?
It's gonna be them.
Oh, it's gonna be orange?
I thought we were friends.
I like this.
Let's get this game going.
For this dungeon, you will not be able
to move on in each section
until you kill every single enemy.
Everyone ready?
Yeah!
Go!
Alright, go, go, go.
Let's go, let's go.
Go, go, go.
Spam your abilities.
A bomb! Bomb!
Watch out for the bomb.
Alright, there's enemies right here.
Easy, easy.
Use your arrows as well.
There we go.
I'll go on top.
Top, top.
I got one.
Oh my god.
Nice, go team.
Go, go, go. Keep goin'!
We're going up.
Purple team's in the lead.
I think we're good.
We're through.
Spam, spam, spam.
Last one, last one.
Last one.
Go, go, go.
Onto the next, onto the next.
We got this, guys.
Guys, enemy on me.
Big enemy on me.
There's big enemies.
We need to, like,
group up on them guys.
Push him in, push him in.
Yeah. Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, this is easy, boys. Easy.
Alright, these two teams are winning.
Oh, my God.
We're cruising.
But it’s not how are you start,
it's how you finish.
Alright. Here we go.
Yo watch out for the bombers!
They're bombers here!
There's so many bombs.
Oh, I'm slamming this guy
with my guitar.
And in case you forgot,
the winning team gets $250,000
that they get to give
to their subscribers.
Fans. I'm doing this for y'all, man.
I’m here.
Yep. Got 'em.
Wait, doors open.
Go, go, go.
If you're wondering
what game all of them are playing,
it's called King of Meat.
King of Meat gave us skins in game,
these custom dungeons,
and even made a secret dungeon
for you to play at home.
Just click the link in description
or scan this QR code.
Available on PlayStation, Xbox, or PC.
I see an arch over here.
I'm taking 'em out.
We did it!
Come on guys,
Thank you King of Meat
for sponsoring this video.
Alright, let's focus.
I don't see anymore.
Go, go, go.
Let's go.
Let's go! Final round.
Alright, time to kill the boss.
Let's go.
Oh! He’s massive.
What's up, big guy?
Focus the boss.
Guys, we need to work together on him.
You guys are on track to be eliminated.
Stop, no, that's not true.
That sucks.
Everyone's already in the boss room
but you guys.
Gotta get ahead.
Let's go. Blow them all up.
Use the explosive barrels.
Yeah, it's getting stuck in my ability.
He’s so low.
Guys, we gotta lock it on the boss.
We got this.
Everyone's on the same level.
Who's gonna finish first?
He's low, he’s low.
Ok. We got it, we got it.
Yeah, he's dead.
Nice, nice.
Go, go, go!
That's the end!
Come on.
[cheering]
We got our first finish!
Oh my God, they made it.
Get on the button.
Come on, everyone!
Yes!
Woo!
Either Grey or Orange
is about to be eliminated!
Go, go, go!
It's gonna be us.
Come on!
I died!
Ok, come on.
Just a couple more.
We're good.
Go, go!
- Where do I go?
- Run in!
Let’s go! Let’s go!
Go, go, go!
Run the door!
I'm running!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
We did it!
No!
Sorry, it didn't work out, Grey team.
It's ok. It happens.
And with that,
you three teams are moving on!
[cheering]
This next round is going to require you
to work as a team.
For this round,
you don't have to kill everything you see,
what you have to do is protect
the most precious cargo on the planet.
This Meat Baby.
Each section in this round,
a player will have to pick up
the meat baby.
If they drop the meat baby,
you'll have to go back
and retrieve it.
He'll be on the rest of your team
to protect that player
and usher them through
while they carry the meat baby.
Alright, any questions?
Wait, is this--
Three, two, one…
Go!
Go, go, go, go!
And they're off.
Oh, the sausage. Wait, grab it.
There is the meat baby.
- Socks. Get it, get it.
- I got it, I got it.
Alright, we'll stay in front.
You stay in the back.
Ok. Wait. What is this?
Watch out. Watch out for that white.
Don't touch those. Oh!
Don't press those platforms.
That slows you down?
Oh my God.
Move up, move up.
Oh wait, guys.
It died!
Alright, you guys
already broke your sausage!
Go back
and get a new one.
Oh, ok. If you take a single hit,
you drop.
Purple team is making it through,
they’re escorting the sausage.
Go, go, go!
Put the sausage on the grill!
Put it down.
Nice. Let's go.
There's a platform.
In the middle!
Ready?
Three, two, one, go!
Ok, watch out! Don’t get hit!
Yeah, yeah!
You got it.
Nice! Let's go.
Yellow, you seem to be in last.
I got it, don’t worry--
Team! Come on, team!
Get your act together, yellow.
Uh, more meat. Where's the meat at?
Oh, it's in there.
Someone has to go above.
Here's the 4th one.
I’m on one!
Got it!
Alright, grab the sausage.
I’ll grab it.
Stay on the platform.
Alright, I'm standing on it.
Wait, wait.
Let me get on it.
There you go.
Now, get ready to switch when I say “go.”
Ok, go, go, go!
Switch, switch!
What are you guys doing?
Why do you always crush?
We're the best team ever!
Since you're so far
in the lead,
I wanna tell you about
our brand-new Feastables bag
that just dropped
in Costco's nationwide.
Here, do you mind giving it a try?
Guys, I’m getting hit!
Oh! Ok, I'm gonna stop talking.
You still got it!
Fry it! Fry that meat!
Throw it in the fire.
Nice!
Ok, next one.
Same thing, same thing.
We have to wait for the platform
to get back.
Do you wanna try Feastables
out of our new Costco bag?
It's gonna wrap
in front of you, BT!
- BT, it’s gonna wrap in front of you--
- No!
Don't die, don’t--
No!
Ok, go, go, go.
Yeah, yeah. Careful.
Just stay on it.
Nice, nice. Keep goin’.
Nice!
Alright, purple’s in the lead again.
Yes, yes!
We're good, we're good.
Throw it on, throw it on!
- Ok. Perfect.
- We're good. Just go.
I'm on the next one.
The platform’s coming from the side.
Platform coming from the side.
Get ready to get on it.
Yeah. Nice, nice, nice.
Now you have you have to cross
to the other side.
Nice, yeah. She made it!
Keep going, go, go, go!
Let's go. Let's go, guys.
Let's go.
Once again,
purple is very much in the lead.
Blue sending now.
Alright, Hyper, send it back!
Let’s go, Hyper!
Yes! I’m through!
Oh my God, you did it!
All three teams are on the same course.
This one's the hardest one.
Good luck.
Ok, we need two people on the thing.
I'm going onto the platform.
This looks easy, right?
Oh my God, it's zombies.
Oh, except for the never-ending army
of mobs coming at you.
There's enemies everywhere!
Fight 'em off, guys.
I’m fighting.
I see enemies at the end.
No, he's good, he's good.
Alright, will purple get it?
I got, I got, I got it!
Alright. Now you gotta get
the whole team across.
We got this, we got this!
Alright, let’s go, go, go!
Guys, let’s go!
First finish!
It’s either orange or yellow.
Who's it gonna be?
Ok, I got it, I got it.
Get on the platform!
Wait, there’s skeletons here.
Ed there's--
You can't let those touch you, Ed!
Ed, jump!
Hold E, hold E!
- No, I died!
- No!
We gotta go back.
Oh, no.
We're so close.
It's right there.
I'll attack the enemies.
You guys just stand!
Don't let go.
You can jump over, probably.
Yellow’s about to do it!
You guys gotta stay on those platforms!
Stay on those platforms.
Jump over.
Yes! Yes!
- Go, go, go! Run!
- Come across!
Everyone come across.
Get on the button!
We’re about to do it.
Come on, come on!
[cheering]
- Let's go!
- King of Meat!
Orange team,
you have been eliminated.
No!
We're gonna steal the moon!
Get the money!
Hey, grab as much as you want,
but I literally have
5 police officers over there,
'cause this is real money,
and they'll just get it back
And with that…
one final challenge stands
between your team
and $250,000 for your fans.
And this final round is simple:
the first team where all 4 players make it
to the top of that hill will win.
You are literally only as good
as your weakest link.
We got no weak links here.
Tens of millions of people watching,
money for your fans on the line,
your team counting on you--
I'm just trying to make you nervous.
I don't get nervous.
Go!
Go, go, go!
Ok, guys, this is it.
We know what to do.
Do not hit the yellow thing.
Oh, I'm dodging, I'm dodging.
Careful of the launch pad here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And for the fire,
I'm using the launch to get across.
Let’s go.
Ok. Watch out.
It's gonna launch us forward.
But we live for that.
Bombs are getting launched
from the side, guys. Watch out!
Big balls!
Oh! Oh my God.
Bro, your team is so far behind.
Dude, are they really?
- Yeah, you're crushing.
- Don't tell me that!
Your team's not even
on the same floor as you.
Oh my God.
Now, I'm not.
Well, never mind.
Oh my God!
Dude, I'm so lost.
I'm not gonna lie. I'm so lost.
I hit it, I hit it.
Oh, we're good. Keep going--
No! I got launched off.
There's, like rolling, uh--
Oh my God, there's big bombs and
they launch you off the map.
Oh, the hammer hit me, bro.
Guys, I don't know where I am.
If you're ahead of us,
just stay there. It's ok.
Go to the trampoline right here, though.
- Ali, right here. The trampolines.
- Yes, yes, I see them.
The stakes are high.
Everything's on the line.
You can tell people are starting
to get a little nervous.
No one wants to be the person
that lets their team down.
Everything is on the line.
Wait, oh, wait.
I'm supposed to be going the other way.
Guys, I'm all turned around!
Where am I?
No, a trampoline right here!
Behind you
Once you make it far enough,
trampolines unlock.
And when you fall,
you can skip right back up.
Am I supposed to go this way?
Oh, wait. Am I going the wrong way?
Are we going the wrong way?
Wait, I just hit a thing.
Wait, come to me, guys.
Yeah, I'm ahead.
Yeah, get on that.
I’ll press it for you.
Ok. Oh, no…
Open!
I got it, I got it.
It's open now.
You're both at the same spot.
It's neck and neck.
I think I hit a checkpoint.
Here guys, I have a trampoline.
Ok, ok.
Can I help you guys when I'm through?
Like what--
Oh, maybe I do.
Hold on…
Devonte jumped off!
I'm gonna go ahead.
I see where a trampoline is.
Wait, I think I messed up.
I hit another trampoline.
Oh, guys, I'm at the top,
so I activated all the shortcuts.
- I'm at the top waiting.
- Ok. I’m coming.
Ok, I'm almost there.
Alright, purple has someone
at the finish line.
Ok. That's fine, that's fine.
I did it. I'm at the end!
Wait, trampoline right here!
Guys, behind you!
Behind, behind us!
Lana, over here. This way.
I’m good.
Ok, I'm up!
Ok. I'm making my way through.
I'm so confused right now.
Oh my God.
Ok, now go forward.
Go forward right here.
Juke this way.
Right here.
Wait, where are you?
We’re here, we’re here!
I’m here, Purpled. I'm here!
Let's go!
Oh my gosh!
[celebrating]
Let's go!
Purple is the winner!
Don’t worry, yellow team, your subscribers
aren't going home empty handed.
We're giving each of you $10,000
to give to your subs however you want.
If you wanna play King of Meat,
just scan this QR code
or click the link in the description.
Hope you enjoyed.